Go! Go!
빨리!
Go! Come on!
어서 뛰어요!
가서 확인해봐!
Go! You, come on!
뛰어요! 어서!
인질들이 없어요!
We got...
지금까지 25명이
탈출했습니다
so far 25 chutes.
- I can't hold her.
- What are you doing?
조종이 안돼!
뭐하는 건가?
보급을 중단하겠다!
Break away! Break away!
Sir, take my hand!
각하, 제 손을 잡으세요!
모두 피해! 어서!
Everybody, break now!
꼼짝마!
- Don't move!
- Let me save him!
구해야 돼요!
저 분이 대통령이라구!
He's the president,
for God's sake!
데려와!
Go get him!
제 손을 잡으세요!
Grab my hand!
Major!
소령, 잡아!
됐습니다
I got you.
대통령을 잡았습니다
보급기가 폭파해?
그 외엔?
We've lost the tanker?
What else?
- They're counting 32 survivors.
- That means they still have hostages.
생존자는 32명입니다
아직 인질이 있단 얘기인데
대통령 가족은?
- What about the first family?
- No word yet.
아직 몰라요
인질이 없으면
놈들은 더 날뛸 텐데
Losing hostages will make
the terrorists more desperate.
Madam Vice President,
we've got "Air Force One" on the line.
각하, 에어포스 원의
연락입니다
This is Vice President Bennett.
We're listening.
부통령 베넷입니다
말씀하세요
우린 미합중국의
대통령을 잡고 있소
I no whold hostage...
the president of the United States
of America.
곧 카자흐의 영공에
들어갈 것이오
Soon we shall enter
the sovereign airspace of Kazakhstan.
에스코트 전투기를
철수시키시오
You will cease your military escort
at the border.
영공을 침해하면
대통령 가족을 처형할 것이오
If you violate our airspace...
I will execute a member
of the first family.
전투 편대를 철수시키세요
Tell our fighters to back off.
본부에 연락해
Get me Ops.
대통령 권한 대행서에
서명하시겠습니까?
You said a presidential incapacity
could be declared by a cabinet majority.
- Would you sign it?
- Under the circumstances.
상황이 상황이니만큼
동조자가 또 있는지
알아보세요
See who else would.
Move! Come on, move!
빨리 빨리 가!
더 빨리!
Fast! Move! Quick! Right here.
여기다
아빠!
여보!
괜찮아, 괜찮아!
- It'll be all right.
- I know.
안돼요
데려가지 말아요!
짐칸에서 꽤 바쁘셨지
안 그래?
You've been very busy downstairs.
Haven't you?
Killing my men.
내 부하들을 죽이느라구
안돼!
You don't wanna do that.
쏘진 못할걸
원하는 건 나니까
I'm what you came for.
Don't forget that.
Then I kill them.
그럼 저들을 죽여야겠군
Or just one.
네가 골라
You pick.
백악관에선 그런 일을
하잖아, 신처럼 말야
That's what you do in the White House.
You play God.
어서 골라
누굴 살릴 거야?
Go ahead.
Which one lives?
- 사랑해
- 사랑해요
Go ahead.
여기까지 온 목적이
이건 아니잖아
You're not here for this.
You want something.
뭐지?
- What is it?
- Radek.
라덱!
- How can I do that? I can't.
- Then you die, the three of you.
그건 할 수 없소
그럼 너희 셋은 죽는다
I'll do anything to save my family.
Don't ask something I can't give!
가족을 살리기 위해선
뭐든 하겠지만
내 능력 밖의 일은
요구하지 마!
The most powerful man on the earth.
Suddenly, there are things you can't do.
세계 최고의 권력자가
못하는 게 있다구?
This is very curious.
Stop with your fucking lies!
웃기는군
거짓말 하지마!
그만!
- Petrov will never give up Radek.
- Petrov is a dog.
페트로프는 절대로
라덱을 포기하지 않아
페트로프는
네 말만 듣는 개잖아?
He does what you tell him.
Tell him to do this.
명령을 내려!
날 이용한 것뿐이야
Petrov used me.
I just wanted to stop the bloodshed.
난 유혈 사태를 막고
싶었을 뿐이구
페트로프는 라덱에게
이기고 싶어했지
He wanted a personal victory.
Petrov hates Radek.
Of course he hates Radek.
Radek is everything he is not.
당연하지, 라덱 장군은
놈과 다르니까
위대하고 힘 있는 분이셔
A great man, a strong man.
Are you saying...
그자가 감히
네 말을 거역할까?
he would refuse you?
You'd be playing right into his hands.
Are you an idiot?
그자 손에 놀아나게 될 걸?
자네 바본가?
You'd make him into a hero.
The man who stopped the terrorists.
덕분에 페트로프는
테러를 막은 영웅...
그보다 날 거부한
영웅이 되겠지
Or better yet,
the man who stopped me.
You talk as if you have nothing
to do with this.
아무 상관없는
사람같이 말하는군
모두 네 탓이야
이 자유라는 전염병!
This is all your doing.
This infection you call freedom.
Without meaning, without purpose.
의미도 목적도 없는 자유!
넌 러시아를 갱과
매춘부 손에 넘겼어
You have given my country...
to gangsters and prostitutes.
You have taken everything from us.
우리에게서
모든 걸 빼앗아 갔어
이제 남은 게 없어
There is nothing left.
당장 전화해
Call him.
싫다, 안해!
안돼!
아이를 내버려둬!
No! Leave her!
Sit!
- No.
- I have no choice.
안돼
어쩔 수가 없어
방법은 간단해
- You have the choice.
- Leave her alone. It's between us.
아이는 놔줘
우리들 문제잖아
You lose a child,
it hollows you out.
아이를 잃으면
가슴에 못이 박히겠지
We're soldiers.
우린 군인이다
날 죽여
You take my life.
Have you no honor?
자넨 명예도 모르나?
다섯을 세겠다
- I'll count to five.
- No!
안돼요!
- It's gonna be all right, honey.
- One.
괜찮아, 앨리스
하나!
- It's gonna be all right.
- Two.
괜찮아
둘!
I'll do it.
하겠어
Yes.
고마워
I'll do it.
전화하겠다구
You just leave my family alone.
내 가족들은
제발 가만둬
Leave 'em alone.
내버려둬
각하, 미합중국
대통령이십니다
Mr. President!
대통령 각하?
We just got an intercept.
대통령께서 페트로프 각하께
라덱을 석방하라 하셨답니다
The president called Petrov
and asked him to release Radek.
- He can't do that!
- He must have no choice.
그럴 수는 없어
선택의 여지가 없었겠죠
We have a choice.
대안은 있소
I have the signatures of the cabinet
attesting to the president's incapacity.
각료 위원들이 서명한...
대통령 직무대행서요
- Sign it and you can overrule him.
- No. I won't do that.
서명해요
그래야 권한이 생겨요
서명 못해요
The United States does not negotiate
with terrorists.
미합중국은 테러범들과
협상하지 않소
It's been our principle
for 25 years.
지난 25년간의 정책을
이제 바꿀 순 없어요
You can't give in to them now.
It'll be open season on
the United States. Many more will die.
그랬다간 더 많은
미국인들이 죽게 될 걸
대통령은
대통령으로서가 아니라...
Jim isn't making this decision as
president, but as a husband and father.
가장으로서 결정을
내렸던 거라구요
History will judge you
by what you do right now.
지금 결정에 따라
역사의 심판도 달라지겠죠
For God's sake, sign it.
제발 서명해요
아니요
못해요
석방됐다
I can now confirm that General Radek
is in the process of being released.
라덱 장군이
석방되고 있다
맙소사!
I repeat. General Radek
is now being released.
반복한다
라덱 장군이 석방된다
네, 라덱 장군이
석방됐습니다
Yes, yes.
General Radek has been released.
I t is confirmed.
확인됐다
장군을 석방시켰어
They are releasing the general.
Now what?
이젠 어쩔 거지?
Now we return to our homeland...
고향으로 돌아가...
라덱 장군이 너희를
최대한 이용할 것이다
where Radek will decide
how best to use you...
now that we know you are willing...
이젠 너희도 협상을
할 것 같으니까
to negotiate.
Our nation needs so many things.
우리나라엔 필요한 게
아주 많아
- You said you were gonna release us.
- Forgive me. I lied.
우리를 놔주겠다고
했었잖아
미안하군
거짓말이었어
들어봐
Listen.
여보!
안돼!
아빠!
맞으셨습니까?
- Sir, are you hit?
- Stay with the major, honey.
소령과 함께 있어
여보!
- Alice, get in the cockpit.
- Lie down.
앨리스, 조종실로 가세요
가만 누워 있어
여보!
그레이스!
아내를 놔줘!
- Let her go!
- Not until Radek is safely away.
라덱 장군이
안전할 때까진 안돼
라덱을 풀어주면 안돼!
Call it off.
Don't give up Radek.
장군이 잘못되면
영부인은 죽는다!
If anything happens to the general,
your wife will die!
안돼, 여보!
동지들, 장군을 모시러
우리 군이 도착했다
곧 장군을
모시게 될 것이다
들었나?
거의 다 끝났어
You hear that?
It's almost over, Mr. President.
Drop the gun!
총 버려!
빨리!
한가지 실수를 했어
You made one mistake when
you killed my pilot, Mr. President.
조종사를 죽였으니
No one left to fly the plane.
이젠 비행기를
조종할 사람은 없다
낙하산도 없구
And no parachute.
Whatever happens...
어쨌든...
당신은 패배자야
난 승리자구
you lose and I win.
내 비행기에서
당장 내려!
Get off my plane!
괜찮아?
You all right?
장군이 안마당으로
나가고 계시다
빨리 러시아 대통령께
전화해요!
Go.
Go! Call Petrov!
서라! 꼼짝마!
라덱을 사살했습니다
They killed him.
Mr. President.
라덱이 죽었습니다
He almost got away.
Did you hear me? Radek is dead.
거의 도망쳤었는데
사살됐습니다
Yes! It's the president.
We have retaken the plane!
대통령께서 비행기를
점령했답니다!
이겼어요!
어떤가?
- How's he doing?
- Not good, sir.
안 좋습니다
자네 비행기를
조종할 줄 아나?
- I don't suppose you know how to fly.
- No, sir.
모릅니다
소령, 따라오게
부조종사가 필요해
- Come along. I'll need a copilot.
- Yes, sir.
알겠습니다
How long since you've flown?
비행은 얼마나 하셨죠?
Twenty-five years.
Little planes. Never jets.
25년, 경비행기만
이런 건 처음이야
Nothing like this.
누구 없나?
- Anybody there?
- We're here, sir.
말씀하십쇼, 각하
누가 이것 좀
조종하게 도와주게
You got somebody
that can help me fly this?
Sir, this is Colonel Jackson. We need
to get you out of hostile territory.
각하, 존슨 대령입니다
밥, 자네군
당장 적의 영공에서
나오셔야 합니다
좋은 생각이네
- Good idea, Bob.
- Look above the central video screen.
중앙에 비디오 스크린을
보십쇼
발광 단추 중 하나가
110로 돼 있어야 합니다
There's a series of L.E.D. numbers.
One of them should read 1-1-0.
- Got it.
- That's your course heading.
찾았네
현재 기수 방향을
나타내는 겁니다
Just below, there's a knob
surrounded by hash marks.
그 아래 눈금 손잡이를
시계방향으로 돌려서
Turn that knob counterclockwise
to 290.
290이 되게 하세요
290!
- We're turning.
- Good.
돌렸네
잘 하셨어요
그럼 카자흐 영공
밖으로 나올 겁니다
- This will take you out of Kazakhstan.
- We're gonna be okay.
이제 괜찮을 거야
We can't land this plane on autopilot,
so we'll need to go over a few things.
자동 착륙을 불가능하니
몇가지 더 말씀드리죠
가장 가까운
착륙지는 어디죠?
Where's the nearest safe landing site?
터키의 인써릭입니다
Incirlik, Turkey.
- General Northwood.
- Madam?
노스우드 장군!
- 네
- 저건 뭐죠?
What's that?
빨간 점은
미그기를 표시합니다
- That red dot represents Migs.
- On course to intercept "Air Force One."
에어포스 원을
파괴하러 출격했군요
Christ! They took off from Aktubinsk.
맙소사, 악투빈스크에서
출격했군
그곳 기지 사령관은
라덱의 추종자에요
The base commander there
is loyal to Radek.
당장 전투기를
출동시키세요
General, send our fighters
into Kazakhstan.
무슨 수를 써서든
각하를 보호하라고 해요
Order them to use any and all means
to protect the president.
마지막엔 스로틀 계기를
중간으로 놓으십쇼
When you're on final approach,
keep the throttles mid-range.
- 알았네
- 각하, 들리십니까?
- Mr. President, can you hear me?
- Yes, Kathryn.
말하게, 부통령
We're tracking six MiGs closing
on your position. I'm sending in...
미그기 6대가 출동해서
F-15기를 출격시켰습니다
our F-15s to protect you.
- Shit!
- Did she say MiGs?
맙소사!
미그기라고 했습니까?
Yes, she said MiGs.
그렇다네
앨리스, 안전띠 매거라
문제가 생긴 것 같아
Get in that seat and put a seat belt on.
We're having trouble.
미그기가 따라 붙었다니
조종을 해야겠는데
These MiGs get closer,
I'm gonna have to maneuver this thing.
How do I get it off auto pilot?
어떻게 자동 조종을
취소시키지?
왼쪽 엄지쪽 손잡이에
단추를 누르십쇼
Push the button on they oke
by your left thumb.
오른쪽으로 회전하겠다
I'll try a little right turn.
천천히 돌리면
회전하게 됩니다
Keep your moves smooth and steady.
It's all flying.
Just step on the ball.
조심스럽게 말이지?
That's right.
Just like riding a bike.
그렇습니다
자전거 탈 때처럼요
Halo Flight, we are cleared to commit,
bearing 0-9-0.
헤일로기, 방위 090로
기수를 돌려라!
전속력으로 발진하라!
Jettison tanks and push it up.
미그기가 얼마나
떨어져 있나?
These MiGs, how far away are they?
'레이다 탐지'
Never mind.
말 안 해도 되겠군
미사일이 따라 옵니다
유도체 발사!
- One coming. Countermeasures activated.
- Left turn.
왼쪽으로 회전!
맙소사!
Jesus Christ!
- We need some help.
- U.S. fighters, this is "Air Force One."
도움이 필요하겠어
미 전투기 편대!
공격받고 있다, 어딨나?
We are under attack.
Where are you?
This is Halo Flight closing
on your position. E.T.A. two minutes.
지금 접근 중이다
도착 2분전!
We may not be here!
2분의 여유가 없어
We're hit!
당했습니다
Christ. We're on fire.
We've got an engine on fire.
맙소사!
엔진에 불이 났어
- Number four engine is on fire.
- Pull the fire handle overhead.
4번 엔진에
불이 붙었다
머리 위쪽의
소화 단추를 누르세요
찾았다!
I got it.
젠장, 기체가
오른쪽으로 기운다
- We're rolling right.
- Left rudder. You have to compensate.
왼쪽 방향타에
균형을 맞춰주세요
1번 엔진에
동력을 올려야 하나?
- Do I pull back on number one engine?
- Negative. You'll slow down.
아닙니다
반대로 끄셔야 합니다
- Trim it out.
- How do I do that?
어떻게?
- Knob. Aft pedestal.
- Jesus Christ!
후미쪽 손잡이로요
하나님 맙소사!
We got a red light.
Looks like we're losing fuel.
또 붉은 점등이
들어왔네
젠장, 연료가 새고 있어
Halo Flight.
모두 적기를 조준하라
Everybody lock a bandit.
Stand by for max range.
발사 준비!
발사!
And Fox Three!
Kill one!
하나 처치했다!
Kill two! Four more bandits
bearing 0-9-0. Halo Flight engage!
두번째 적기 제거!
앞으로 4대, 조준!
Ha, ha! Good guys are here.
우리 편이 왔어
- Bug out west. We'll cover you.
- You got it.
에어포스 원! 서쪽으로
이동하라, 엄호하겠다
알았다!
- Sir, pull up! You got one on your tail.
- Get him off my tail!
각하, 기수를 올리세요
꼬리 쪽에 한대 있습니다!
빨리 없애 버려!
미사일이 발사됐다
고도를 올리십쇼!
Missile away.
- Break left and climb!
- Shit! Sir, we've lost countermeasures.
맙소사! 발사할
유도체가 없습니다!
This is "Halo 2. " They've lost
countermeasures. I'm going in.
유도체가 떨어졌다
엄호하겠다!
헤일로 2호기가 떨어졌다!
Two's down! "Halo 2"is down!
"Air Force One, "
are you still with us?
에어포스 원, 무사한가?
Yes! We're sti I l here.
무사하다
그렇게는 안 된다,
망할 자식!
Not so fast, you son of a bitch!
나머지 미그기 3대는
퇴진했습니다!
The last three MiGs
are bugging out, sir.
We're clear!
이제 안전합니다!
- 밥, 듣고 있나?
- 네
- Bob, are you still there?
- Yes, sir.
문제가 생겼네
Got a little problem here.
My rudder is sluggish.
방향타 반응이 이상해
Let me look.
제가 한번 보겠습니다
Oh, man!
맙소사, 굉장히 많이
파손됐습니다
Sir, you're torn up pretty bad.
Do you have any elevator control?
승강타는 조절됩니까?
그것도 안 좋네
게다가 연료까지 새고 있어
It's sluggish, too.
And we're still losing fuel.
알겠습니다
We got a problem up here.
Sirs, "Air Force One" is badly hit.
에어포스 원의
손상이 심합니다
저런 상태로는
착륙은 불가능합니다
With the damage,
there's no way they can land.
I'm sorry, sir.
죄송합니다, 각하
도와줘서 고맙네
- Thanks for your help.
- I'll stay on your wing, sir.
옆을 지키겠습니다
Take it straight and steady
until we figure out what to do.
방법을 강구할 때까지
계속 비행하십쇼
Sir.
각하...
You did great.
정말 잘하셨습니다
They can't control the plane. Engines
are failing and they're losing fuel.
이젠 불가능합니다
엔진은 물론 연료까지 새니
There must be something
we can do to help them.
분명 무슨 방법이
있을 겁니다
장군, 저건 우리 항공
활주팀 아닌가?
- Is that our airstrip strike team?
- Yeah. Why?
맞습니다, 왜요?
I just had a wild idea.
묘안이 있네
Time is critical.
Start turning north.
시간이 없다
북으로 기수를 돌려라
- You'll get more details en route.
- Yes, sir.
세부 사항은 가면서
알려주겠다
알겠습니다
Change of orders acknowledged.
명령 전달 받았습니다
Try to hold your heading, sir.
They'll rejoin in about 25 minutes.
현재 코스를 고수하십쇼
25분 뒤에
합류하게 될 겁니다
All right.
알았네
위험한 작전입니다
- We know it's risky.
- Understood.
알고 있네
But we are all out of options.
다른 도리가 없습니다
아빠?
그래, 앨리스
Yeah, baby?
괜찮아요
모두 다 잘 될 거예요
It'll be okay.
Everything's gonna work.
Concerned Americans have gathered
at the White House...
많은 국민들이
백악관 앞에 모여...
to await word on the president
and his family.
대통령 가족의 소식을
기다리고 있습니다
But CNN has learned
that "Air Force One"...
그러나 현재 에어포스 원은
착륙이 불가능할 정도로...
is severely crippled
and virtually unlandable.
파손이 심하며
대통령 가족을 실은 채...
Sources report that the first family
is still trapped on board.
공중 구조 작전을
기다리고 있습니다
And a daring midair rescue operation
is said to be underway.
"Air Force One, "this is "Liberty 2-4"
approaching on your left side.
여기는 자유 24호기
들립니까?
- Do you read?
- "Air Force One." Loud and clear.
잘 들린다
Gibbs, they're here.
Get the door.
깁스, 구조팀이야
문 열게
알겠습니다
고도는 만 피트, 속도는
2백 노트로 맞추십시오
- We'll need 10,000 feet and 200 knots.
- We've got to get her slowed down.
속도를 늦추어야겠어
"Air Force One"and "Liberty 2-4, "
this is "A WACS Blue Star:"
여긴 AWACS 블루스타!
레이더에 잘 잡히고 있다
We have you in radar contact.
자유 24호기!
연료가 거의 바닥났다
"Liberty 2-4, "
they're almost out of fuel.
알았다, 에어포스 원!
날개 균형을 잡아라
Roger.
"Air Force One, "keep the wings level.
If the engines fail, sacrifice altitude
to maintain airspeed.
엔진이 꺼지더라도
속도만은 유지해야 한다
준비!
Ready!
첫 구조원이 출발했다
" Liberty 2-4," ram p leader.
First man is on his way.
Back up. Easy.
천천히요
"Air Force One, " come left, six.
에어포스 원!
약간 왼쪽으로 돌아라
속도는 어때?
- How's my speed?
- It's good. See if you can hold it.
좋습니다
그대로 유지하세요
A little more left, sir.
Three, two, stop.
좀 더 왼쪽으로
셋, 둘, 됐습니다!
Take my arm! Pull me in!
팔을 잡아줘요!
여기야!
당겨줘요!
Come on! Come on!
좀 더!
후크를 떼주시오
- Unhook me.
- I got it.
됐소!
Good.
구조선 연결 완료!
각하는 어디 계시죠?
"Liberty," locked in.
Where's the president?
조종실에 계시오
Up in the cockpit.
- We lost another engine.
- "Liberty," we lost another engine.
엔진이 하나가 또 꺼졌어
자유 24호기!
엔진이 하나 더 꺼졌다
알았다
"Liberty 2-4." Acknowledged.
각하, 가셔야 합니다
Sir, time to go.
- Who's gonna fly the plane?
- I'll take care of that, sir. Got it.
그럼 비행기는
누가 조종하구?
제가 처리하겠습니다
됐습니다
출발!
Go!
두번째 낙하병이
출발했다
Ramp to pilot.
Second P.J.'s on the way.
- Mr. President, this way!
- My family first.
각하, 가십쇼!
가족부터 보내야 해
- Sir, I have orders to take you off.
- Them first.
하지만 명령을
받았습니다
가족부터 보내!
"Blue Star," the third parajumper
is boarding "Air Force One:"
3번 낙하병이
에어포스 원에 탑승했다
구조 대기하라
- Standing by for recovery.
- Roger. Moving into receiver position.
알았다
인수 위치로 이동한다
아빠?!
- Dad?
- You'll be all right, honey.
괜찮아, 앨리스
- Promise?
- Promise.
정말이죠?
그럼
눈 감아
Close your eyes.
넌 할 수 있어
꼭 잡아
You can do it.
Just hold on tight.
It's okay. Don't worry.
괜찮아요
걱정마세요
무사할 거야
She's okay.
아빠!
조금만 참아요
- Hang on!
- Ramp to pilot. We got her!
영애를 받았다!
바로 뒤따라갈게
I'm right behind you.
Come on there!
됐습니다
조금만 더요
Hang on. Good.
- You're next, sir.
- Him next. He's wounded.
다음은 각하십니다
부상자부터 보내게
알겠습니다
먼저 가십쇼
- You go.
- Come on, Shep. Come on, pal.
어서 가게, 쉐퍼드
We've lost another engine.
엔진이 또 하나
나갔습니다
You're sinking too fast. We only
have time for one more retrieval.
하강 속도가 너무 빨라
한 사람밖에 구할 수 없다
고도 3천 피트
2분후 추락한다
We're passing 3,000 feet.
Impact in less than two minutes.
Get the president out of there!
대통령 각하를 모셔라
Right here.
조금만 더!
됐습니다
Easy there.
He's on.
무사히 탔군
준비하십쇼
가셔야 합니다
- Get your arms ready. I t's time to go.
- What about the other team?
저 친구들은?
There's no time.
I can only take one more.
한분 구할 시간 밖에
없습니다
No! We're all going!
안돼, 모두 가야 해!
That's impossible, sir.
I have to take you.
불가능 합니다
빨리 가세요
각하!
It's time to get you off this plane.
Go, sir.
가셔야 할 때입니다
어서 가세요!
Go!
Please go!
부탁입니다
It was you?
자네였어?
구조선 내놔!
- Give me the strap!
- I trusted you with my life.
난 생명을 걸고
자넬 믿었었어
So will the next president.
Now, give it to me.
다음 대통령도 그럴 테지
빨리 내놔!
고도가 너무 떨어져
케이블을 끊어야 한다
We have to release the cable.
We're descending from 1200 feet.
난 비행기에서
꼭 내리고 말겠어
I'm getting off this plane!
Seven hundred!
현재 고도 7백!
5백 피트!
Five hundred!
We have to pull up!
줄을 끌어 올려야 한다
"Blue Star:"
"Air Force One"is down.
블루스타!
에어포스 원이 추락했다
I repeat.
"Air Force One"is down.
반복한다
에어포스 원은 추락했다
"Liberty 2-4,"
do you have the president?
대통령은 구조됐나?
Right. You can do it.
체중을 한쪽으로
실어 보세요!
- "Liberty," do you have the president?
- Stand by.
대통령 각하는 구출했나?
기다리십시오
몸을 돌리세요!
조금만 더요!
잡아요
Hang on!
구조했습니다!
We got him!
"Liberty 2-4"is changing call signs.
"Liberty 2-4"is now...
자유 24호기의
호출명을 변경합니다
이제부터
'에어포스 원'입니다
"Air Force One"!
Mr. President, welcome aboard, sir.
대통령 각하
탑승하신걸 환영합니다!
더 많은 영화정보를 원하시면 www.82movie.com에 지금 방문하세요!!